{
    "id": "8ebd32a5799449148ec66ff82a79bb0c",
    "title": "Idioms Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Janet and Peter are getting married. I heard it straight from the ....................... mouth.",
            "description": "Straight from the horse's mouth means from the most reliable source of information.",
            "answers": [
                "elephant's",
                "horse's",
                "camel's"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9222f2f7dfc44b788675462e597100db"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wanted the party to be a secret but my sister let the ......................... out of the bag.",
            "description": "To let the cat out of the bag is to reveal a secret by mistake.",
            "answers": [
                "dog",
                "bird",
                "cat"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ff4d5ba225444c1db1d36489d7010085"
        },
        {
            "question": "The moment she started ....................... me up, I knew that she wanted to gain a favor.",
            "description": "To butter someone up is the praise them.",
            "answers": [
                "pampering",
                "barking",
                "buttering"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a0c0ef3714d741989dbc614341c72c5d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The two brothers are always pulling each other's .........................",
            "description": "To pull someone's leg is to tease them.",
            "answers": [
                "ear",
                "leg",
                "hand"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "53fb03368e2845298f51620c038a6851"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don't trust him. He is a ........................ in sheep's clothing.",
            "description": "A wolf in sheep's clothing is a dangerous person who pretends to be harmless.",
            "answers": [
                "wolf",
                "fox",
                "dog"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b02968de862c49658490e604c9cc72f9"
        },
        {
            "question": "He won the race ...................... down.",
            "description": "When you manage to do something hands down you accomplish it without a lot of effort.",
            "answers": [
                "hands",
                "legs",
                "head"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8a8b2167a82d4d09a43707349e145efc"
        },
        {
            "question": "By taking action against him for your failure you are just .................. up the wrong tree.",
            "description": "To bark up the wrong tree is to pursue a misguided course of action.",
            "answers": [
                "cutting",
                "peeling",
                "barking"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c5bd8bd77b6a40d3ae005d9eb4064402"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don't try to make fun of him. He ........................... off the handle pretty easily.",
            "description": "To fly off the handle is to become very angry.",
            "answers": [
                "runs",
                "flies",
                "drives"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "31907d004ffd40e1bff01b92c827ed15"
        },
        {
            "question": "That laptop cost me ...................",
            "description": "If something costs you an arm and a leg, it is very expensive. ",
            "answers": [
                "an arm and a leg",
                "an eye and an ear",
                "a finger and a toe"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "87cf40a02eed4a059d166ccfc7f72fda"
        },
        {
            "question": "I hate having to tell him what I really think of him but I have to ............................ the bullet now.",
            "description": "To bite the bullet is to force yourself to do something unpleasant.",
            "answers": [
                "fire",
                "bite",
                "dodge"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "96f109ff29fb46f8a6ebdabc22ab361a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The indulgent mother turns a ...................... to her son's faults.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "blind eye",
                "black eye",
                "partial eye"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2f703c20bd314285bab8b529396415cd"
        },
        {
            "question": "The enemy was armed to the .................... yet our soldiers managed to beat them.",
            "description": "When you are armed to the teeth, you are extremely well equipped.",
            "answers": [
                "teeth",
                "neck",
                "nose"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "eaa684ce06054541adea63ff7ae67779"
        }
    ]
}